[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which former US President said I know Im getting better at golf because I hit  fewer spectators.", "correct_answer": "Ford", "incorrect_answers": ["George W. Bush", "Carter", "Eisenhower"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This organ expands up to 500 times its normal size during the pregnancy.", "correct_answer": "The uterus", "incorrect_answers": ["The stomach", "The ovaries", "The bladder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This actor was voted Worst Actor for 1992 at the Golden Raspberry Awards.", "correct_answer": "Sylvester Stallone in Stop! Or My Mom Will Shoot!", "incorrect_answers": ["Michael Douglas in Basic Instinct", "Kevin Costner in The Bodyguard", "Jack Nicholson in Hoffa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Suns surface temperature is roughly 10,000 degrees F. The temperature at the Suns core, however can be as high as what?", "correct_answer": "2,000,000 degrees F.", "incorrect_answers": ["25,000 degrees F.", "100,000 degrees F.", "500,000 degrees F."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Robert Downey, Jr. became the first actor to be nominated for an Academy Award for the portrayal of a previous Oscar nominee. What actor did he portray in a 1992 movie?", "correct_answer": "Charlie Chaplin", "incorrect_answers": ["Dean Martin", "Fred Astaire", "Spencer Tracy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The cross on the Swiss flag is red.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Over the years we have become accustomed to hearing the train whistle. Who invented the train whistle?", "correct_answer": "George Washington Whistler", "incorrect_answers": ["Thomas Jefferson", "Edward Land", "Thomas Alva Edison"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which wedding anniversary is known as the Golden Wedding Anniversary, or Golden Wedding Day?", "correct_answer": "50th anniversary", "incorrect_answers": ["60th anniversary", "40th anniversary", "25th anniversary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1988 anime feature, set in Tokyo, is about a military project that endangers the city when it turns a biker gang member into a rampaging psychopath.", "correct_answer": "Akira", "incorrect_answers": ["Heavy Metal", "Felix", "Gummo"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If there is a one way street and there are two cars going the opposite direction, is either of the drivers breaking the law?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular American martial artist did Jean-Claude Van Damme portray in the 1988 movie Bloodsport?", "correct_answer": "Frank Dux", "incorrect_answers": ["Stuart Wilson", "Bob Anderson", "Gordon Richiusa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what country is picking your nose in public more acceptable than blowing your nose?", "correct_answer": "Japan", "incorrect_answers": ["France", "Phillipines", "Iran"]}]